

# CONTACT



Pisano 196, San Borja, Lima, Peru



+51 976 444 471



ggarciarivera09@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gonzalogar ciariv92/

# **SKILLS**

- Cross-functional teamwork
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Flexible and Adaptable
- Multitasking Abilities
- Research methods
- Business continuity planning
- Qualitative and quantitative analysis
- MS Office
- Classroom experience
- Video edition

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native language	
English:	C1
Advanced	
Chinese (Mandarin):	A1
Beginner	
German:	A1
Beginner	

# Gonzalo Garcia Rivera

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Gifted multitasker with solid record of accomplishment in several departments, strategies and key projects. Experienced in financial reporting, project management, market research, deepening partnerships and boosting sales with creative and proactive approaches. Successful business professional with demonstrated track record consulting. Skilled at teaching, integrating ideas and customising approaches to support specific means and goals.

# **WORK HISTORY**

## Sales Manager

07/2022 - Present

South Spirits Ltd. - Seville, Spain

 Establishment of business proposal with potential buyers and suppliers in the European and Asian regions.

# **Marketing Assistant**

05/2021 - 06/2022

#### Embassy of India in Lima - Lima, Peru

- Elaboration of financial reports from local regions for potential business opportunities among Indian and Peruvian companies and commercial guilds.
- Built partnerships between Indian, Peruvian and Bolivian export promotion councils and companies to promote bilateral trading.
- Oversaw preparation and management of commercial events of different industries.
- Managed 20+ daily customer calls through effective use of call handling technology.

#### **Business Development**

05/2019 - 04/2021

# CG Consultoria Minera - Lima, Peru

- Analysed and resolved complex resource management issues for optimised scheduling.
- Reported and consolidated company financial performance.
- Reviewed files, records and historic data to obtain required business information for development requests.

# **Account Executive**

10/2018 - 12/2018

#### Transcendent Solutions LLC - California, United States

- Performed excellent sales services by offering bespoke product advice to meet exact customers' needs.
- Provided friendly, engaging and professional retail service to 5+ customers per shift.
- Welcomed over 25 customers professionally and offered excellent advice and product demonstrations.

## **Audit Assistant**

12/2016 - 01/2017

#### UHY Urbano Ventocilla & Asociados - Lima, Peru

• Assisted 3 auditors in performing audit jobs from planning to finalisation

within the areas of project, fuel and warehouse planning.

#### **Finance Assistant**

05/2016 - 09/2016

#### Andina de Radiodifusión (ATV) - Lima, Peru

- Evaluated office processes and suggested efficiency improvements that reduced expenditures by 35%.
- Organised budget documentation and tracked expenses to maintain tight business controls.
- Interacted and built collaborative relationships with marketing, sales and operations staff.

## **Financial Planning Practitioner**

05/2015 - 05/2016

#### Andina de Radiodifusión (ATV) - Lima, Peru

- Built and updated financial models to support ongoing budgeting and forecasting processes, analyse complex information and process real-time data.
- Improved financial status by analysing results, monitoring variances and recommending financially-sound actions.
- Strategised and led financial planning and operations for 5 businesses.

#### **Teacher's Assistant**

10/2013 - 01/2014

## **ESAN University** - Lima, Peru

- Collected qualitative and quantitative data with rigorous methodology.
- Supported teachers with academic research for university classes.

#### **Cost and Budget Practitioner**

01/2013 - 04/2013

## Compañía Minera Ares SAC - Lima, Peru

- Compiled financial data for business forecasting and budgeting.
- Collaborated with business management to set and control annual budgets.

# STARTUP INITIATIVE

#### GalaxyMaths - Lima, Peru

05/2020 - 12/2022

## **Business Development Manager**

- Elaboration of financial and business management reports about the financial performance of the company regarding each new partnership made with a new sponsorship.
- Identified and closed new business opportunities through strategic networking, enhancing valuable client bases.
- Provided recommendations and executed strategies for revenue growth opportunities, leading to increased profitability.

# **EDUCATION**

**Master of Science**: Disruptive Innovation, 04/2019 **Hult International Business School** - San Francisco, USA

Master of Science: International Business, 08/2018
Hult International Business School - San Francisco, USA

• Member of Cooking, Music and Social Help clubs

Bachelor of Science: Economic, 10/2014

ESAN University - Lima, Peru

• Member of Beta Gamma Sigma honour society